export const shortsData = [
    {
        id: "short1",
        youtubeLink: "https://youtube.com/embed/AoUUnpoFviA",
        questions: [
        {
            questionText: "What is a mole in chemistry?",
            correctAnswer: "A unit of measurement",
            options: ["A type of reaction", "A unit of measurement", "A type of compound", "A type of element"]
        },
        {
            questionText: "Which scientist's name is associated with the concept of a mole?",
            correctAnswer: "Amedeo Avogadro",
            options: ["Isaac Newton", "Albert Einstein", "Dmitri Mendeleev", "Amedeo Avogadro"]
        },
        {
            questionText: "What does one mole of any substance contain?",
            correctAnswer: "Avogadro's number of entities of that substance",
            options: ["One gram of that substance", "Avogadro's number of entities of that substance", "The molar mass of that substance", "The atomic number of that substance"]
            },
        ],
    },
    {
      id: "short2",
      youtubeLink: "https://youtube.com/embed/JDH5UFcINKY",
      questions: [
        {
            questionText: "If you have the balanced chemical equation: 2H\(_2\) + O\(_2\) -> 2H\(_2\)O, how many moles of O\(_2\) are needed to react with 4 moles of H\(_2\)?",
            correctAnswer: "2 moles",
            options: ["1 mole", "2 moles", "4 moles", "8 moles"]
        },
        {
            questionText: "In the balanced chemical equation: 4Fe + 3O\(_2\) -> 2Fe\(_2\)O\(_3\), if you have 8 moles of Fe, how many moles of Fe\(_2\)O\(_3\) can you produce?",
            correctAnswer: "4 moles",
            options: ["2 moles", "4 moles", "8 moles", "16 moles"]
        },
        {
            questionText: "In the balanced chemical equation: 2H\(_2\) + O\(_2\) -> 2H\(_2\)O, how many moles of H\(_2\)O are produced if you have 2 moles of O\(_2\)?",
            correctAnswer: "2 moles",
            options: ["1 mole", "2 moles", "4 moles", "8 moles"]
        },
        // More questions as needed...
      ],
    },
    {
        id: "short3",
        youtubeLink: "https://youtube.com/embed/PvKSEQ8RYdE",
        questions: [
          {
              questionText: "Which formula would you use to calculate the number of moles if you know the mass of the substance and its molar mass?",
              correctAnswer: "\(n = m/M\)",
              options: ["\(n = m/M\)", "\(m = n * M\)", "\(M = m/n\)", "\(C = n/V\)"]
          },
          {
              questionText: "If you know the number of moles and the molar mass of a substance, which formula allows you to calculate its mass?",
              correctAnswer: "\(m = n * M\)",
              options: ["\(n = m/M\)", "\(m = n * M\)", "\(M = m/n\)", "\(C = n/V\)"]
          },
          // More questions as needed...
        ],
      },
      {
        id: "short4",
        youtubeLink: "https://www.youtube.com/embed/9L_p1NN3rOc",
        questions: [
          {
              questionText: "Which one of these statements about the mole is incorrect?",
              correctAnswer: "A mole of a substance is always smaller in mass than a mole of another substance",
              options: ["A mole of any substance contains Avogadro's number of entities", "The molar mass of an element in g/mol is numerically equal to the element's atomic mass in atomic mass units", "A mole is a measure of the number of atoms in exactly 12 grams of carbon-12", "A mole of a substance is always smaller in mass than a mole of another substance"]
          },
          {
              questionText: "What is the relationship between the mole and Avogadro's number?",
              correctAnswer: "A mole contains Avogadro's number of entities",
              options: ["A mole is smaller than Avogadro's number", "A mole is larger than Avogadro's number", "A mole contains Avogadro's number of entities", "There is no relationship between a mole and Avogadro's number"]
          },
          {
              questionText: "Avogadro's number is crucial for the concept of a mole. What does it represent?",
              correctAnswer: "The number of atoms in exactly 12 grams of carbon-12",
              options: ["The number of atoms in exactly 12 grams of carbon-12", "The number of particles in exactly one gram of a substance", "The number of moles in one gram of a substance", "The number of molecules in one liter of a substance"]
          },
          // More questions as needed...
        ],
      },
    // More shorts as needed...
  ];
  